

CONTACT ME AT

92,Thirukkulam melkarai, Dharasuram, Kumbakonam. 612702

agathi.nv@gmail.com

https://be-bees.github.io/agathiyan/

+91 86104 45677

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/agathiyan nv/

SKILLS SUMMARY



80% JavaScript

80% Angular, TypeScript

NPM, Bootstrap, jQuery, D3.js

Gitlab, Github

50% CouchDB

Node.js, Express.js

CERTIFICATION

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022 by Udemy

JavaScript Algorithms and Data
Structures Masterclass by Udemy

SQL Masterclass: SQL for Data
Analytics by Udemy

Certified SolidWorks Associate (CSWA) by Udemy

AREA OF DEVELOPING

- JavaScript
- Angular 12+

PERSONAL TRAITS

- Following directions
- Engage from the beginning
- Problem analyzing attitude

INTERESTS

- Learning by internet surfing
- Cooking

AGATHIYAN VENKATRAMAN

Web Developer

PERSONAL PROFILE

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the product industry. Admirable expertise in Responsive web application development, JavaScript and Angular. To collaborate with a talented team, continuously learn and grow, and contribute to the success of organizations

WORK EXPERIENCE

Programmer

Chainsys Corporation | July 2021 - Present

- Building responsive web app with self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components
- Cooperating with the back-end developer in the process of building the RESTful API

Product: Smart App Builder | Chainsys, 2021 - Present

• Smart App Builder is a low code / No code platform for building powerful Web and mobile applications. With the help of drag and drop design we can easily prepare the data model and forms as our requirements. If needed we can able to modify the pages with developer environment concept. It uses dataZap's(ETL) ready to use Smart Data Templates for Data Extraction, Data Loading and Data Mappings with target enterprise applications.

Shell Project | Chainsys, 2021 - 2022

• We created the Time management and tracking web and mobile based application for shell. We have enabled notification, calendar and workflows for this application. All the approves will be done in both web and mobile.

Collins Aerospace Project | Chainsys, 2021 - 2023

 Project management application and dashboards for Collins aerospace system. They requested a forms to show their fight details with running status. Here we have enabled high security configurations and deployments

Lecturer

MASS Polytechnic College | June 2019 – March 2021

 Trained SolidWorks and Educated Strength of Materials, Design of machine elements for undergraduate students as a part of curriculum of the Mechanical Engineering

PRIMARY SKILLS

- Having 2+ years of experience in HTML, CSS3, and JavaScript
- Experience of front development frameworks like Angular
- Knowledge of libraries such as Bootstrap, jQuery, D3.js.
- Basics of the back-end technologies like API's and databases such as Couch Db
- Knowledge of version control systems especially GIT
- Have exposure in CI/CD activity tools like gitlab, Jenkins
- Knowledge of (Node.js, Express)
- Unit-test the code and debug the application.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Anjalai Ammal-Mahalingam Engineering College

B.E. Mechanical Engineering | Aug 2014 - May 2018 | 7.93 Gpa

- Studied theoretical and analytical part of Mechanical Engineering, project planning and ethics
- Worked on my projects with ARK solutions, Inc